[cheerful music]
- We are on fire this month.
这个月我们真是火力全开。
We've already got our Sunshine Girl kayaking badge,
我们已经拿到了阳光女孩划艇徽章，
oh, our cookie selling badge, our community service badge.
哦，还有饼干销售徽章，社区服务徽章。
- If you call cleaning out your mom's car community service.
如果你把清理你妈妈的车叫做社区服务的话。
- Hey, I said you could keep anything you found.
嘿，我说过你可以留下你找到的任何东西。
- I got 32 cents and a hard French fry.
我找到了32美分和一个硬邦邦的法式薯条。
- Dibs!
我要了！
This one isn't hard.
这个不难。
This one's hard!
这个难！
Ow, ow.
哎哟，哎哟。
[horn honks] - That's my mom.
[喇叭声]那是我妈。
Bye, Sunshine Sisters.
再见，阳光姐妹。
all: Whoo-dee-whoo-dee- whoo-wah!
所有人: 呼哈哈呼哈哈呼!
- Bye. - Bye.
再见。
- Bye. - See you later.
- My two favorite scouts
再见。
and their fearless troop leader.
待会儿见。
Get in here. [all chuckle]
我最喜欢的两个童子军和她们无畏的领队。
See how happy they look with all their badges?
进来吧。[众人笑]
Just think, if you guys were scouts,
想想看，如果你们也是童子军，
you'd be in on this hug too.
现在也能加入这个拥抱了。
[grumbling]
[咕哝声]
- Not into it. - No thanks.
- 不感兴趣。- 谢了，不用。
- No time.
- 没时间。
- [scoffs] What do you mean?
- [嘲讽]你什么意思？
All you have is time.
你们有的是时间。
When I was painting that fence earlier,
刚才我刷栅栏的时候，
you stood there and literally watched it dry.
你们就站在那儿，真的看着它变干。
- That's only because we were finished
- 那是因为我们刚好完成了
watching the grass grow.
看草生长。
- Yeah, right after we finished watching you cut it.
- 是啊，就在我们看完你割草之后。
- [sighs] Boys, there is a long tradition of Honor Scouts
- [叹气] 孩子们，我们家有悠久的荣誉童军传统。
in our family.
我曾是荣誉童军。
I was an Honor Scout.
我父亲曾是荣誉童军。
My father was an Honor Scout.
我祖父也是荣誉童军。
His father was an Honor Scout.
- 这已经够久了。
- That seems long enough.
- 你父亲甚至在多年前就给你买了荣誉童军的制服，
- Your father even bought you Honor Scout uniforms years ago,
就盼着有一天你会被童军精神所感染。
just hoping for the day you'd get bitten by the scout bug.
- 对不起，爸爸。我们真的不是童军那块料。
- Sorry, Dad. We're just not scout people.
对不起，爸爸。我们真的不适合当童子军。
- Fine. No internet for a month.
好吧。那我一个月不能上网。
all: What? - I meant for me!
什么？——我是说我自己！
I'm a failure as a father, and I don't deserve it.
我作为父亲很失败，我不配拥有它。
- Look, I bet you guys would love being scouts.
听着，我打赌你们会喜欢当童子军的。
Last month we did a ton of fun stuff.
上个月我们做了很多有趣的事情。
Like, we went hiking--
比如，我们去徒步——
- I'm out.
我不干了。
- You guys should give it a chance.
你们应该试试看。
- Would we get to play with this fancy poking stick?
我们可以玩这个花哨的戳戳棒吗？
- That's not a fancy poking stick.
- 那不是什么高级的戳戳棒。
- Yeah, sure it is. - Ow, ow.
- 是啊，当然是。 - 哎哟，哎哟。
Ow, ow, ow.
哎哟，哎哟，哎哟。
That is fancy.
那确实很高级。
- It's not a poking stick.
- 这不是戳戳棒。
This is the Sunshine Girls' Truth Stick.
这是阳光女孩们的真理棒。
- We took a sacred oath of honor
- 我们作为阳光姐妹团的一部分，
as part of our Sunshine Sisterhood pact.
立下了神圣的荣誉誓言。
The person holding it is always bound to tell the truth.
持有它的人必须永远说实话。
- Really? Can I try?
- 真的吗？我可以试试吗？
The Sunshine Girls don't do anything
阳光女孩们不做任何
that would interest us in any way.
能引起我们兴趣的事情。
Hey, it works.
嘿，这东西有效。
- Hmm, that's too bad.
- 嗯，那太糟糕了。
Because I sold the most Sunshine Girl cookies,
因为我卖出了最多的阳光女孩饼干，
and won five tickets
赢得了五张
to the Ele-Funk Nation concert on Saturday.
周六Ele-Funk Nation演唱会的门票。
- [gasps]
- [倒抽一口气]
[both trumpeting]
[两人吹喇叭]
- We love Ele-Funk. Check out my shirt.
- 我们超爱Ele-Funk。看看我的T恤。
- Yeah, we'd love to go.
- 是的，我们很想去。
- That's why I suggested to Mae that she takes all of us.
- 所以我才建议梅带我们所有人一起去。
- Yes. - Sweet.
- 是的。 - 太好了。
- Now that's what being a quad is all about.
- 这就是四人组的真正意义。
Thanks, Dawn.
谢谢，Dawn。
- But...since you guys
- 但是...既然你们
have no interest in what the Sunshine Girls do, then--
对Sunshine Girls做的事情没兴趣，那么--
- Ah, the truth is we were wrong about the Sunshine Girls.
- 啊，事实是我们对Sunshine Girls的看法错了。
They're great. - Yes, please forgive us.
她们很棒。 - 是的，请原谅我们。
We will never doubt the Sunshine Girls again.
我们再也不会怀疑Sunshine Girls了。
- I was the one who tried to flush a watermelon
- 是我试图把西瓜冲进马桶。
down the toilet.
把它从我这儿拿走！
Get this thing away from me!
[玻璃破碎声]
[glass shatters]
不是我。
It wasn't me.
别让我捡起那根棍子，
Don't let me pick up the stick,
否则你们就会知道是我干的。
or you guys will know it was me.
[欢快音乐]
[upbeat music]
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[口哨声]
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[cheerful music]
- You'll never catch me!
你永远抓不到我！
[panting] Safe!
[panting] 安全！
- Okay, Tom, I don't want to play tag anymore.
好吧，汤姆，我不想再玩捉迷藏了。
- I don't have internet anymore, Anne.
我不再有网络了，安妮。
What am I supposed to do?
我该怎么办？
- Oh, E.F.N.
哦，E.F.N.
Oh, you know, I'm so jealous you guys got tickets.
哦，你们拿到票了，我真羡慕。
Ha, I'm always down to groove to some funk in the trunk.
哈，我随时都准备好跟着后备箱里的放克音乐摇摆。
[trumpets]
[小号声]
- What's wrong with Mom?
- 妈妈怎么了？
- I'll call the doctor.
- 我打电话给医生。
- Oh, oh, you know, we haven't been to a concert in years.
- 哦，哦，你知道的，我们已经好几年没去音乐会了。
Honey, maybe we should go.
亲爱的，也许我们应该去。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Oh, honey, I would love to.
哦，亲爱的，我也很想去。
- Got you! You're it!
- 抓到你了！轮到你了！
[trumpets]
[小号声]
- I can't do this anymore!
- 我再也受不了了！
- What is that?
- 那是什么？
- It's what I'm wearing to the concert.
- 这是我打算穿去音乐会的衣服。
all: Ohhh.
所有人: 哦~~
- We cannot be seen with her looking like that.
- 我们不能和她那样打扮的人一起出现。
- Yep, Dawn says it'll make us the Ele-Funkiest people there.
- 是的，Dawn说这会让我们成为那里最时髦的人。
[trumpets]
[小号声]
- You know, Mae, if you don't like it,
- 你知道吗，Mae，如果你不喜欢，
you should tell Dawn how you really feel.
你应该告诉Dawn你的真实感受。
- Yeah, so we don't have to go to the concert
是的，所以我们不必去音乐会
with you looking like that.
和你这样子。
And because we care about your feelings.
而且因为我们关心你的感受。
- I get it.
我明白。
Even I wouldn't want to be seen with me.
即使我也不想和我自己一起被看到。
But I can't tell Dawn.
但我不能告诉Dawn。
You know how she is when she gets an idea in her head.
你知道她一旦有了一个主意在她脑子里会怎样。
- Oh, yeah. - She can be pushy.
哦，是的。
- I didn't say pushy. - But we know what you meant.
她可能会很坚持。
- Mae, you're her best friend.
Mae，你是她最好的朋友。
You need to be honest with her
你需要对她诚实
and tell her just like you told us
就像你对我们说的那样告诉她
that you think she's pushy.
你认为她有点强迫症。
- That was your word, not mine.
- 那是你的词，不是我的。
- Who's ready to get Ele-Funky?
- 谁准备好去Ele-Funky了？
[trumpets]
[小号声]
Oh, I wish the concert was tonight.
哦，我真希望音乐会是今晚。
Maybe they'll pull us up onstage where everyone can see us.
也许他们会把我们拉上舞台，让所有人都能看到我们。
I mean, we do look pretty great, don't we, Mae?
我的意思是，我们看起来确实很棒，不是吗，Mae？
- Yeah, I love it.
- 是的，我喜欢。
- Mae doesn't love it.
- Mae并不喜欢这样。
- What are you talking about? Of course she loves it.
- 你在说什么呢？她当然喜欢。
I think I know my best friend.
我觉得我了解我的好朋友。
Right, Mae?
对吧，Mae？
- Mae?
- Mae？
- Uh...
- 呃...
- Mae.
- Mae。
- Uh...
- 呃...
- Mae?
- Mae？
- Uh...
- 呃...
- Mae!
梅！
- Uh...
呃...
- I got this.
我来处理。
Mae!
梅！
I thought I had it.
我以为我搞定了。
- No, I got this.
不，我来处理。
The truth, Mae.
真相，梅。
- Ugh, I don't like it.
呃，我不喜欢这样。
There, I said it.
好了，我说出来了。
- Then why would you lie to me earlier
那你为什么之前要对我撒谎，
and tell me you did like it?
然后你为什么要早些时候对我撒谎，告诉我你喜欢它？
- Yeah, why, Mae?
- 是的，为什么，Mae？
- Because I thought it would be easier
- 因为我以为如果我告诉你我喜欢它，事情会变得简单些。
if I told you that I liked it.
我撒谎是因为有时候你可能会有些...
I lied because sometimes you can be a little...
强迫。
pushy.
- 强迫？
- Pushy?
我不强迫人。我怎么强迫人了？
I'm not pushy. How am I pushy?
- 我说过强迫吗？
- Did I say pushy?
你就是强迫。
You're pushy.
- 哇。
- Wow.
哇。
What else have I pushed you into?
我还逼你做了什么？
- Nothing, nothing.
没有，没有。
- Was it when we dressed as peanut butter and pickles
是我们万圣节扮成花生酱和腌黄瓜的时候吗？
for Halloween?
万圣节？
- Uh...
呃...
Everyone knows pickles don't go with peanut butter.
大家都知道腌黄瓜和花生酱不搭。
It's peanut butter and jelly.
应该是花生酱和果酱。
I should have been jelly!
我应该是果酱才对！
- I see.
我明白了。
Well, I'm not going to a concert
好吧，我不会和不诚实的人一起去音乐会的
with someone who can't be truthful.
花生酱，出局！
Peanut butter, out!
哦，男孩们也不去了
Oh, and the boys aren't going either.
什么？
all: What?
哇，花生酱，冷静点
- Whoa, PB, settle down.
反正我也不想和这么强势的人一起去
- Well, I don't want to go with someone who's so pushy anyway.
泡菜，出局
Pickles, out.
等等，更正一下，果酱，出局
Wait, scratch that. Jelly, out.
这做得太好了
This is so well made.
谢谢！嗯，我要愤然离场了
- Thank you!
谢谢！
Um, I'm storming out over here.
呃，我正要离开这里。
How 'bout you storm out over there?
你怎么不在那边离开？
- Fine, I don't want to storm out that way anyway.
好吧，反正我也不想那样离开。
[both grunt]
[两人哼声]
- Did we just lose our concert tickets?
我们是不是丢了音乐会的票？
- Did we just ruin Dawn and Mae's friendship?
我们是不是破坏了Dawn和Mae的友谊？
- Did we just get hungry
我们是不是饿了
for peanut butter and pickle sandwiches?
想吃花生酱和腌黄瓜三明治？
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[cheerful music]
- I can't believe we're going to miss
我不敢相信我们要错过
the greatest concert ever.
史上最棒的演唱会。
- Well, maybe we shouldn't worry.
嗯，也许我们不必担心。
This is Dawn and Mae we're talking about.
我们说的是Dawn和Mae。
They're BFFs. It'll blow over.
她们是死党。这事会过去的。
- Hey, is that your box of Mae memories?
嘿，那是你装满Mae回忆的盒子吗？
- It was.
曾经是。
And now it's in the "Maeste" basket.
现在它进了“Maeste”篮子。
- Wait, Dawn, you don't want to throw
等等，Dawn，你不想就这样放弃
your friendship with Mae away.
你不想放弃你和Mae的友谊。
[straining]
[用力]
- Really, dude?
- 真的吗，伙计？
Oh. Ooh!
哦。哦！
How many friendship rocks are in here?
这里面有多少友谊石？
- Friendship rocks? None.
- 友谊石？一个也没有。
It's just birthday cards and stuffed animals.
只有生日卡片和毛绒玩具。
- Help us.
- 帮帮我们。
[all straining]
[大家都在用力]
- We're just gonna set this on the floor.
- 我们只是把它放在地板上。
- Okay, okay.
好的，好的。
- [groans] - Ooh.
（呻吟声）哦。
- Okay, we have got to start exercising.
好吧，我们得开始锻炼了。
- Dawn, don't do this.
Dawn，别这样。
Mae is your best friend. - [scoffs]
Mae是你最好的朋友。（嗤之以鼻）
- She's the pickles to your peanut butter.
她是你的花生酱里的泡菜。
- She's the rocks to your friendship.
她是你们友谊的基石。
- She's the tickets to our concert.
她是我们的演唱会门票。
- Oh, we can still totally go to that concert.
哦，我们还是可以去看那场演唱会的。
- Yes. - Awesome!
是的。太棒了！
- Ele-Funk! [all trumpeting]
Ele-Funk！[所有大象齐鸣]
- As soon as Mae apologized to me for lying
Mae一为我撒谎道歉
and admits she's wrong about calling me pushy.
并承认她称我为强硬是错的。
[sad trumpeting] - Hold on.
[悲伤的大象鸣叫] - 等等。
Let's keep our trunks up.
让我们保持我们的象鼻高举。
[all trumpeting]
[所有大象齐鸣]
We got Mae to confront Dawn.
我们让Mae面对Dawn。
I'm sure we can get her to apologize.
我相信我们可以让她道歉。
- Apologize?
道歉？
No way!
不可能！
Dawn should be apologizing to me.
Dawn应该向我道歉。
- Well, you're the one who told Dawn she was pushy.
- 嗯，是你告诉Dawn她很强势的。
- Yeah, maybe you shouldn't have done that.
- 是的，也许你本不该那么做。
- You're the ones who pushed me
- 是你们逼我
to tell Dawn she was pushy.
去告诉Dawn她很强势的。
You said to be assertive and stand up to Dawn.
你们说要坚定立场，勇敢面对Dawn。
- You should have been assertive and stood up to us then.
- 那你当时就应该坚定立场，勇敢面对我们。
So really this is all your fault.
所以实际上这都是你们的错。
- Well, I'm not apologizing to her.
- 嗯，我不会向她道歉的。
Apologize. Mm-hmm.
道歉。嗯哼。
- Fine, if Mae won't apologize to Dawn,
好吧，如果Mae不会向Dawn道歉，
we'll get Dawn to apologize to Mae.
我们就让Dawn向Mae道歉。
- [laughing hysterically]
[狂笑]
Me apologize to her?
我向她道歉？
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Good one.
说得好。
- Now we're never gonna get to that concert.
现在我们永远也去不了那个音乐会了。
- Oh, ye of little faith.
哦，你这缺乏信心的人。
If Dawn wants an apology from Mae,
如果Dawn想要Mae的道歉，
she's gonna get an apology from Mae.
她就会得到Mae的道歉。
[phone rings]
[电话铃响]
- I'll get it!
- 我来接！
Hello.
喂。
Oh, hi, Mae.
哦，嗨，Mae。
Dawn, it's Mae.
Dawn，我是Mae。
How are you?
你好吗？
Oh, you have a little bit of a cold,
哦，你有点感冒了，
so you don't sound like yourself?
所以听起来不像平时的你？
Oh, that's-- that's too bad, Mae.
哦，那真是——太糟糕了，Mae。
Dawn, it's Mae.
Dawn，我是Mae。
She has a little bit of a cold,
她有点感冒，
so she doesn't sound like herself.
所以听起来不像她自己。
- Mm-hmm.
- 嗯哼。
- Hello, Dawn! This is Mae.
- 你好，Dawn！我是Mae。
I'm just calling to tell you how terribly sorry I am
我打电话是想告诉你
for lying to you
我对你撒谎是多么抱歉
and saying you were so pushy.
还说你很强势。
You are definitely not pushy.
你绝对不是强势的人。
- I get it, Mae.
- 我明白，Mae。
You called to mock me with that insincere apology.
你打电话来是用那不真诚的道歉来嘲笑我。
Faking sick and using that voice you know I hate.
装病还用那种你知道我讨厌的声音。
You know, I thought you were better than that.
你知道的，我以为你比这更好。
Bye, Mae!
再见，Mae！
- Ooh, some cold, huh?
- 哦，感冒了，是吗？
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- What's that, Dawn?
- 那是什么，Dawn？
You were doing a lot of screaming at practice
你在练习时大喊大叫
and your voice is a little hoarse?
你的声音有点沙哑？
Yeah, that's too bad.
是啊，那太糟糕了。
Oh, she's right here.
哦，她就在这儿。
- What?
- 什么？
- Hello, Maeeee.
- 你好，Maeee。
- Wrong horse.
- 找错马了。
- Hello, Maeeeee.
- 你好，Maeee~~。
- No, she's a little hoarse.
- 不，她声音有点嘶哑。
- I got it. - Okay.
- 我明白了。- 好的。
- [high-pitched] Hello, Maeeee.
- [尖声] 你好，Maeee。
- Well, the phone calls didn't work.
- 嗯，打电话没起作用。
- I'm not sure why.
- 我不清楚为什么。
- You did eight different horses,
- 你模仿了八种不同的马，
and three of them were British.
其中三匹是英国马。
- Oh, you got that, huh?
- 哦，你注意到了，是吗？
- Well, let's just hope this works.
- 好吧，我们就希望这能奏效。
- Hey, guys, what's up?
- 嘿，伙计们，怎么样？
- Look, Mae baked you a "Maeke-up" cake.
- 看，Mae给你做了一个“Maeke-up”蛋糕。
And isn't it a cute picture of you two besties?
这不是你们俩好朋友的可爱照片吗？
- Mae knows I hate this picture.
- Mae知道我讨厌这张照片。
I mean, I look terrible.
我是说，我看起来糟透了。
This isn't a make-up cake.
这不是一个补救蛋糕。
This is a make-fun-of-me cake.
这是一个取笑我的蛋糕。
- Wait.
等等。
- Wait, no, no, no, no.
等等，不，不，不，不。
- Wait a minute.
等一下。
We both look terrible.
我们俩看起来都很糟糕。
Mae would never use this photo to apologize.
Mae绝不会用这张照片来道歉。
What are you three up to?
你们三个在搞什么鬼？
all: Us three?
我们三个？
- Help, help, help, help!
救命，救命，救命，救命！
- Okay, ohhh! [all groaning]
好吧，哦！
- Easy, easy. - I can't get--
轻点，轻点。我拿不到——
- Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
- You wouldn't happen to be trying
你不会是故意想
to get me and Mae to make up
让我和Mae和好
just so you could go to the concert?
只是为了你能去音乐会吧？
- That's ridiculous.
那太荒谬了。
- [neighs] Noooo!
不！
- We're quads. We have a bond.
我们是四胞胎，我们有羁绊。
- That hurts, Dawn. That hurts.
那很伤人，Dawn。真的很伤人。
- Okay, just so we all know we can trust each other,
好吧，为了确保我们都能互相信任，
let's make a quad pact.
让我们立一个四胞胎的誓约。
- Sure. - Why not?
当然可以。
- Yeah, we're up for a pact.
为什么不呢？
- Great.
是的，我们支持这个约定。
Now, let's promise each other
太好了。
we're gonna stick together as quads
现在，让我们互相承诺
and none of us are going to that Ele-Funk concert
我们将作为四胞胎团结在一起
under any circumstances.
并且在任何情况下都不会去那个Ele-Funk演唱会。
Quad pact!
四胞胎约定！
all: Quad pact.
四胞胎约定。
- Thank you.
谢谢你们。
Pushy.
太强硬了。
Why would Mae ever get the idea that I'm pushy?
梅怎么会认为我强硬呢？
- You know what?
你知道吗？
We can't let Dawn use a quad pact
我们不能让道恩利用四人协议
to push us around like we're some...
把我们像……
cake.
蛋糕一样推来推去。
We need to take our own advice
我们需要听从自己的建议
and stand up to her.
并勇敢地面对她。
both: Yeah! - Come on.
两人: 对！ - 来吧。
Dawn, we need to tell you something.
道恩，我们有话要告诉你。
- Me first.
我先说。
Look at us.
看看我们。
We've always been a team.
我们一直是一个团队。
Always standing by each other,
总是互相支持，
even when we don't agree. - Speaking of which--
即使我们有分歧。
- So I just want to thank you guys for sticking by me through this whole Mae thing.
说到这个——
- You know, about that-- - And I'm really sorry that I doubted you.
所以我想感谢你们在这整个Mae的事情上支持我。
You guys are the best brothers a girl could ever ask for.
你知道，关于那件事——
[growling]
我真的很抱歉我怀疑过你。
So you were saying? all: Nothing.
你们是最好的兄弟，一个女孩能要求的最好的。
- Cool. Thanks again.
- 酷。再次感谢。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[cheerful music]
[愉快音乐]
[doorbell chimes]
[门铃声]
- Hey, Dawn. - Hi, Dawn.
- 嘿，Dawn。 - 嗨，Dawn。
- Hey, ladies.
- 嘿，女士们。
Thanks for coming over to take my mind off Mae
谢谢你们过来帮我忘掉Mae和今晚的演唱会。
and tonight's concert.
- 关于那个，我们在想
- About that, we were thinking
有什么比
what better way to take your mind off
不去演唱会更好的方式来忘掉它呢？
not going to the concert,
不去音乐会，
than by going to the concert?
那还有什么比去音乐会更好的方式呢？
- With us!
- 和我们一起！
both: We got tickets!
我们都拿到了票！
- No way!
- 不可能！
We're going to see Ele-Funk Nation!
我们要去看Ele-Funk Nation的演出！
[all trumpeting]
[所有人欢呼]
[sad trumpeting]
[悲伤的欢呼]
- What's wrong?
- 怎么了？
- I'm sorry. I can't go.
- 对不起。我去不了。
I made a quad pact.
我做了一个四人约定。
My brothers and I promised each other
我和我的兄弟们互相承诺
that we wouldn't go to the concert.
我们不会去参加那个音乐会。
[sad trumpeting]
- We are going to that concert.
- 我们要去那个音乐会。
- Are we sure we're doing the right thing?
- 我们确定我们做的是对的吗？
- Absolutely.
- 当然。
- Then why are we dressed in these old uniforms
- 那为什么我们穿着这些旧制服
Dad bought us?
爸爸给我们买的？
- So we could sneak out of the house.
- 这样我们可以偷偷溜出家门。
- But what about the quad pact?
但是四人协议怎么办？
If we're doing the right thing,
如果我们做的是正确的事，
why do we have to sneak?
为什么我们得偷偷摸摸的？
- Because part of being a quad
因为作为四人组的一部分
is caring about each other.
是关心彼此。
And when you care about each other,
而当你关心彼此的时候，
you don't hurt each other.
你就不会伤害对方。
And if Dawn knew we were going to the concert without her,
如果Dawn知道我们没有她去音乐会，
it would hurt her.
她会感到受伤。
And then she would hurt us.
然后她会伤害我们。
- So we're helping her not hurt us,
所以我们是在帮她不伤害我们，
which helps us and her.
这样对我们和她都有好处。
Quad pact complete.
四人协议达成。
- I don't understand it,
我不明白，
but that's never stopped me before.
但这从来没阻止过我。
Let's roll.
我们走吧。
It's hard to roll!
滚动很难！
[ripping]
（撕裂声）
Ah.
啊。
Ah, much better.
啊，好多了。
You guys should do the rip.
你们应该撕开它。
- We're fine.
- 我们没事。
We don't want to look like idiots with ripped shorts.
我们不想穿着破短裤看起来像个傻瓜。
Well, off to our very first Honor Scout meeting.
好了，去参加我们的第一次荣誉童子军会议。
- Wow, you guys decided to become Honor Scouts?
- 哇，你们决定成为荣誉童子军了？
- Yeah, I mean, we didn't have anywhere else
- 是啊，我的意思是，今晚我们没有别的地方可去，
we were going tonight,
既然我们要遵守我们的约定。
since we're honoring our pact and all.
- 这些制服怎么回事？
- What's up with those uniforms?
- 它们没那么紧。
- They aren't so tight.
- 那为什么你们的腿是蓝色的？
- Then why are your legs blue?
- 那为什么你的腿是蓝色的？
- Our legs aren't blue.
- 我们的腿不是蓝色的。
[both gasp, scream]
[两人同时惊呼，尖叫]
Our legs are blue! Our legs are blue!
我们的腿是蓝色的！我们的腿是蓝色的！
- Do the rip! Do the rip!
- 撕开！撕开！
- All right! [ripping]
- 好吧！[撕裂声]
- [both sigh]
- [两人叹气]
- Well, we'll be on our way.
- 那么，我们该走了。
- See? My brothers are honoring the pact.
- 看？我的兄弟们正在遵守约定。
I have to, too.
我也必须这么做。
- What about our pact?
那我们的约定呢？
- Yeah, we're Sunshine Girls.
对啊，我们是阳光女孩。
We've made a pact to form a loyal sisterhood.
我们约定要建立一个忠诚的姐妹情谊。
both: Whoo-dee-whoo-dee- whoo-wah!
呼迪呼迪呼哇！
- Oh, don't pull our secret greeting on me.
别对我用我们的秘密招呼。
Look, I know about our bond.
听着，我知道我们的纽带。
But my quad bond is stronger.
但我的四重纽带更强大。
- Are you sure?
你确定吗？
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- So let me get this straight.
所以让我搞清楚。
You all decided to join Honor Scouts tonight?
你们决定今晚一起加入荣誉童子军？
- Yep.
- 是的。
- And you all sat on the same cactus
- 然后你们都坐在同一个仙人掌上
and ripped your pants?
还把裤子扯破了？
- Well, not at the same time, but yes.
- 嗯，不是同时，但确实如此。
- And this isn't something you cooked up
- 这也不是你们为了逃避可能和妹妹达成的协议而编造的吧？
to get out of a pact you might have made with your sister?
所有人：童子军的荣誉。
all: Scout's honor.
- [乌鸦叫声]
- [cawing]
但你们可能不应该向Dawn提起音乐会的事。
But you probably shouldn't mention the concert to Dawn.
呃，不想再提了。
Uh, don't want to rub it in.
呃，不想炫耀。
- That's fine.
那很好。
Until Dawn apologizes to me, I won't be talking to her.
直到Dawn向我道歉，我不会和她说话。
Oh.
哦。
Oh, now if you'll excuse me,
哦，现在如果你们不介意，
I'm gonna go get myself a tusk of nachos.
我要去给自己拿一盘玉米片。
- Great. All we have to do
太好了。我们只需要
is keep Dawn from ever apologizing to Mae.
防止Dawn向Mae道歉。
- Should be easy.
应该很容易。
Not like they'll ever be in the same room anytime soon.
他们不太可能很快在同一个房间里。
- Now that I'm here, I feel really guilty
- 现在我在这里，我真的感到很内疚
about breaking the quad pact.
关于打破那个四人协议。
Maybe I shouldn't have come.
也许我本不该来的。
- Come on, Dawn, your brothers are never gonna know.
- 别担心，Dawn，你兄弟们永远不会知道的。
They're at a scout meeting ten miles from here.
他们在一个十英里外的童子军会议上。
- Yeah.
- 是啊。
Or ten feet from here. Look.
或者十英尺外。看。
- What are they doing here?
- 他们在这里做什么？
- I can't believe it.
- 我简直不敢相信。
I'm gonna go over there and give them a piece of my mind.
我要过去给他们点颜色看看。
But I won't.
但我不会去。
Because I'm not supposed to be here either.
因为我也不应该在这里。
Ohh, they're looking this way! Go, go, go, go, go, go, come on.
哦，他们在往这边看！快走，快走，快走，快走，快走，快走，快点。
Stampede, people! Stampede.
快跑，大家！快跑。
- Push harder or you're not gonna make it.
- 再用力推，不然你过不去的。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝声]
Uh, oh, no. This is not good.
呃，哦，不。这不太妙。
Natalie, June, I'm stuck.
娜塔莉，琼，我卡住了。
- We'll meet you upstairs. - Wait, upstairs?
- 我们在楼上见。 - 等等，楼上？
Okay, relax.
好吧，放松。
Maybe the boys won't see me.
也许男孩们不会看到我。
- Is that Dawn?
- 那是Dawn吗？
- She broke our pact.
- 她打破了我们的约定。
- So did we.
- 我们也一样。
- Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
- 是的，但她不知道。
I'm gonna go over there and give her a piece of my mind.
我要过去给她点颜色看看。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, big fella.
- 哇，哇，哇，大个子。
- We're not supposed to be here either.
- 我们也不应该在这里。
All we can do now is enjoy the concert
我们现在能做的就是享受音乐会，
and hope she doesn't see us.
并希望她没看到我们。
- Hey, scouts, one of the herd is caught in the elevator.
嘿，小组成员们，有一只羊被困在电梯里了。
You need to go help.
你们需要去帮忙。
- Uh...
呃...
We're off duty.
我们下班了。
- Scouts are never off duty.
童子军是永远不会下班的。
- Well, we're home-scouted, so our rules may be a little--
嗯，我们现在是在家里，所以我们的规则可能有点...
- You made a sacred scout pact. Now go. Go, go, go, go.
你们已经立下了神圣的童子军誓言。现在去吧。快去，快去，快去。
Hang on, they're coming.
坚持住，他们来了。
- Okay, we gotta make a pact.
好吧，我们得立个誓言。
No more pacts.
不再立誓言了。
- Hey, concertgoer in need,
嘿，需要帮助的音乐会观众，
we just came from our scout meeting to help you.
我们刚从我们的侦察会议过来帮助你。
- Oh!
哦！
Dawn?
Dawn？
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
- Oh, you know, just waiting for the elevator doors to open.
哦，你知道的，只是在等电梯门打开。
Which they should any second now.
它们应该随时都会开了。
Or they'll continue to the floor below.
或者它们会继续到下一层。
- No, what are you doing at the concert?
不，你在音乐会上做什么？
- You know, I could ask you the same thing.
你知道，我也可以问你同样的问题。
In fact, I will.
事实上，我会的。
What are you doing at the concert?
你在音乐会上做什么？
- Well, we were at our meeting--
我们在开会——
- What? Liars! You broke the quad pact.
什么？骗子！你们打破了四人协议。
- You broke the quad pact, too.
你也打破了四人协议。
Don't get all high and mighty on us.
别在我们面前装高尚。
- I am not all high and mighty.
我没有装高尚。
- Well, you lied and said that you weren't going,
你撒谎说你不去，
so we couldn't go.
所以我们也不能去。
- Yeah, and then you went.
是啊，然后你自己去了。
- And you went, too.
你也去了。
Is anybody getting off on this floor?
有没有人在这层楼下车？
- So we're done here?
我们说完了吗？
- Oh, we're not done here.
哦，我们还没说完呢。
How could you lie to me?
你怎么能对我撒谎？
You said Dawn was okay with you coming to the concert.
你说道恩不介意你来听音乐会。
- And you told us you wouldn't talk about it
而且你告诉我们不会在道恩面前谈论这件事。
in front of Dawn.
所以...
So...
你们俩都对我们撒谎了。
- You guys lied to both of us.
这很糟糕。
That's pretty messed up.
这真是太混乱了。
Seriously?
真的吗？
- This whole thing started
这一切都是因为
because you told me to stand up to Dawn,
你让我去面对Dawn，
and then you couldn't even do it yourselves.
而你们自己却连这点都做不到。
- You're right. This is all our fault.
你说得对，这都是我们的错。
We shouldn't have been so judge-y about your headpiece,
我们不应该对你的头饰那么评头论足，
although it does have its obvious drawbacks.
尽管它确实有明显的缺点。
- But you guys are right.
但你们说得对。
I should have spoken up for myself.
我应该为自己发声。
- Am I really so pushy that everyone is afraid
我真那么霸道吗，以至于大家都害怕
to tell me how they feel?
告诉我他们的真实感受？
- It's not that you're pushy.
并不是你霸道，
It's just you're so enthusiastic about things,
只是你对事情太热情了，
I don't want to let you down.
我不想让你失望。
- Mae is right.
梅说得对。
We don't want to let you down either.
我们也不想让你失望。
- Look, I really appreciate that,
听着，我真的很感激，
but I have to say...
但我必须说……
Will you please let me down?
你们能不能让我失望一次？
Look, you four are the most important people in my life.
听着，你们四个是我生命中最重要的人。
Guys, I'm sorry I broke the quad pact.
伙计们，对不起我打破了四人契约。
all: Us too.
我们也是。
- And, Mae, I'm sorry if my enthusiasm pushed you away.
还有，Mae，如果我的热情让你感到疏远，我真的很抱歉。
I know peanut butter and pickles are over.
我知道花生酱和泡菜的时代已经过去了。
But will you be my jelly?
但你能做我的果酱吗？
- I'll always be your jelly.
我会一直是你的果酱。
[funk music plays]
[放克音乐响起]
[elephant trumpets]
[大象鸣叫]
- Now, who's ready to get Ele-Funky?
现在，谁准备好来点Ele-Funky？
[all trumpet]
[所有人吹喇叭]
♪ ♪
[elephant trumpets] - ♪ Yeah, come on ♪
[大象吹喇叭] - ♪ 耶，来吧 ♪
♪ ♪